[
  {
  "id":"1",
  "question":"What animal is chicken made from",
  "answer": "Chicken"
},
  {
  "id":"2",
  "question":"What animal is beef made from",
  "answer": "Cow"
},
  {
  "id":"3",
  "question":"What animal is pork made from",
  "answer": "Pig"
},
  {
  "id":"4",
  "question":"Do you ever feel",
  "answer": "Like a plastic bag?"
},
  {
  "id":"5",
  "question":"Pc or Mac",
  "answer": "Pc"
},
  {
  "id":"6",
  "question":"Why are there no question marks for the questions",
  "answer": "Punctuation is lame"
},
  {
  "id":"7",
  "question":"When was the war of 1912",
  "answer": "1912"
},
  {
  "id":"8",
  "question":"What should you always remember",
  "answer": "The alamo"
},
  {
  "id":"9",
  "question":"WHat should you never forget",
  "answer": "9/11"
},
  {
  "id":"10",
  "question":"Do you believe in the moon landing",
  "answer": "Are you implying the moon is real"
},
  {
  "id":"11",
  "question":"Did you know 25 questions is a lot",
  "answer": "25 questions is a whole lot"
},
  {
  "id":"12",
  "question":"How many people does it take to change a lightbuld",
  "answer": "Hopefully just one"
},
  {
  "id":"13",
  "question":"What is green and shaped like a bucket",
  "answer": "Green bucket"
},
  {
  "id":"14",
  "question":"What is red and shaped like a bucket",
  "answer": "Green bucket in disguise"
},
  {
  "id":"15",
  "question":"What is green and has four wheels",
  "answer": "Grass"
},
  {
  "id":"16",
  "question":"Who discovered the moon",
  "answer": "Idk it isnt documented"
},
  {
  "id":"17",
  "question":"Who ate the first apple",
  "answer": "Eve"
},
  {
  "id":"18",
  "question":"Which Eevee-lution is the best",
  "answer": "Jolteon"
},
  {
  "id":"19",
  "question":"Which pokemon starter is the best",
  "answer": "Trick question there are no electric starters (except in yellow)"
},
  {
  "id":"20",
  "question":"Why am i not asleep right now",
  "answer": "I am working on this program"
},
  {
  "id":"21",
  "question":"What liquid is the best liquid",
  "answer": "Water"
},
  {
  "id":"22",
  "question":"Which MMO is the best MMO",
  "answer": "FFXIV"
},
  {
  "id":"23",
  "question":"Did i mess up my json file",
  "answer": "I hope not"
},
  {
  "id":"24",
  "question":"What is the square root of 4",
  "answer": "Two"
},
  {
  "id":"25",
  "question":"Is a pound of steel or a pound of feathers heavier",
  "answer": "Steel"
  }
]
